Finding aid for the R.B. Kitaj papers LSC.1741
UCLA Library Special Collections
- 3. Writings about R.B. Kitaj, 1980-2004; 15 boxes
  - Interviews
    - BBC: Words of Faith -- James Hyman (Box 149, Folder 16)
    - Neither Fool, Nor Naïve, Nor Poseur-Saint: Fragments on R.B. Kitaj by Frederic Tuten, 1982 (Box 154, Folder 19)
    - Ritz Newspaper, 1984 (Box 161, Folder 4)
    - Interview with Frederic Tuten -- photocopy, 1981 (Box 164, Folder 10)
    - Interview with Frederic Tuten -- photocopy, 1981 (Box 169, Folder 8)
  - Works by Others
    - The Poetry of Nikos Stangos by David Plante -- draft, undated (Box 149, Folder 3)
- 4. Publicity Materials, 1963-2007; 16 boxes
  This series consists primarily of press clippings and other related publicty regarding R.B. Kitaj's career.
  - No Subseries assigned
    - Assorted clippings (1 of 5), ca. 1965 - 1985 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Assorted clippings (2 of 5), ca. 1965 - 1985 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Assorted clippings (3 of 5), ca. 1965 - 1985 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Assorted clippings (4 of 5) (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Assorted clippings (5 of 5), ca. 1965 - 1995 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Assorted publicity materials, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Assorted publicity materials, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Parnassus: Poetry in Review Journal (1 of 2), 1995 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Parnassus: Poetry in Review Journal (1 of 2) (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Oversize publicity materials, 1963, 1966 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Filmhouse publication, ca. 1995 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous, 1981 - 1984 (Box 116, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous, 1973 - 1974 (Box 116, Folder 5)
    - Publicity (1 of 2) (Box 116, Folder 7)
    - Publicity -- miscellaneous (1 of 1), 1967 - 1975 (Box 116, Folder 8)
    - Publicity (2 of 2), 1997 - 2004 (Box 116, Folder 8)
    - Publicity (1 of 4), 1963 - 1970 (Box 116, Folder 12)
    - Publicity (2 of 4), 1973 - 1974 (Box 116, Folder 13)
    - Publicity (3 of 4) (Box 116, Folder 14)
    - Publicity (4 of 4), undated (Box 116, Folder 15)
    - The Times -- Letter to the editor, 12 July 1980 (Box 132, Folder 14)
    - List of works -- New York holdings, 2004 (Box 136, Folder 22)
    - Prospectus for an illustrated edition of The Waste Land by T.S. Eliot, 2007 (Box 136, Folder 29)
    - Reviews and annotated articles, 1979 - 1999 (Box 138, Folder 3)
    - Royal Academy of Arts Magazine, Autumn 2005 (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - Publicity (1 of 3), 1966 - 1969; 4 items. (Box 138, Folder 26)
    - Publicity (2 of 3), September 1962; 1 item. (Box 138, Folder 27)
    - Publicity (3 of 3), 1965 - 1969 (Box 138, Folder 28)
    - Lists of works -- miscellaneous, undated (Box 138, Folder 29)
    - Publicity (Box 138, Folder 31)
    - Publicity, 1974 (Box 138, Folder 32)
    - IHR Ideal Home Range -- Kitaj napkin wrappers, undated (Box 139, Folder 18)
    - Publicity, 1964 - 2000 (Box 147, Folder 15)
    - Trajekte -- magazine (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - R.B. Kitaj -- catalogue proof, 1978 (Box 148, Folder 3)
    - Publicity, 1962 - 1979 (Box 149, Folder 14)
    - Publicity, 1975 - 1976 (Box 149, Folder 15)
    - Publicity, 1963 - 1967 (Box 149, Folder 17)
    - Publicity (Box 149, Folder 19)
    - Publicity, 1965 (Box 149, Folder 20)
    - Publicity, 1961 - 1975 (Box 149, Folder 21)
    - Publicity, 1971 - 1975 (Box 149, Folder 22)
    - Publicity, 1969 - 1979 (Box 149, Folder 23)
    - Publicity (Box 149, Folder 24)
    - Publicity, 1978 - 1979 (Box 149, Folder 26)
    - Publicity, 1977 (Box 149, Folder 28)
    - Publicity, 1979 (Box 149, Folder 31)
    - Publicity, 1976 - 1977 (Box 149, Folder 32)
    - Transcript of a dialogue between Michael Andrews and Victor Willing -- Morality and the Model, undated (Box 150, Folder 5)
    - Publicity, 1975 - 1979 (Box 150, Folder 6)
    - Reports and articles, 1966 - 1978 (Box 150, Folder 7)
    - Publicity, 1976 - 1979 (Box 150, Folder 8)
    - Publicity, 1979 (Box 150, Folder 9)
    - Royal Academy of Arts -- calendar (Box 153, Folder 15)
    - Publicity, 1963 - 1976 (Box 157, Folder 15)
    - Narrative Paintings: Figurative Art of two generations selected by Timothy Hyman, 1979 (Box 157, Folder 16)
    - Publicity -- newspapers (Box 157, Folder 17)
    - The Times Literary Supplement: Shakespeare's Day, 23 April 1964; 1 item. (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - The Times Literary Supplement: Shakespeare's Day, 23 April 1964; 1 item. (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - The Times Literary Supplement: The Critical Moment, 26 July 1963; 1 item. (Box 159, Folder 3)
    - London Review of Books, 22 March 1990; 3 items. (Box 159, Folder 4)
    - The Times Literary Supplement: The Changing Guard, part 1, 6 August 1964; 1 item. (Box 159, Folder 5)
    - The Times Literary Supplement: The Changing Guard, part 2, 3 September 1964; 1 item. (Box 159, Folder 6)
    - Publicity, 1984 (Box 161, Folder 2)
    - Publicity, 1982 - 1983 (Box 161, Folder 3)
    - Reviews and Critics (1 of 2), 1980 - 2005 (Box 161, Folder 7)
    - Reviews and Critics (2 of 2), 1980 - 2005 (Box 161, Folder 8)
    - The Guardian -- R.B. Kitaj wrapping paper, 12 May 2007 (Box 165, Folder 9)
    - First Diasporist Manifesto -- publicity (Box 171, Folder 13)
    - LA Weekly, September 1997 (Box 185, Folder 1)
    - Art/World, April/May 1979; 2 items. (Box 185, Folder 2)
    - The Guardian: Weekend, 25 April 1998 (Box 185, Folder 3)
    - Arnolfini Review, 1979 (Box 185, Folder 4)
    - The London Review of Books, January 1980 (Box 185, Folder 5)
    - Jewish Chronicle, 15 November 1991 (Box 185, Folder 6)
    - Kunstavisen, January/February 2001 (Box 185, Folder 7)
    - Jewish Chronicle -- excerpt, 21 September 2001 (Box 185, Folder 8)
    - Le Petit Canard, September - November 1995 (Box 185, Folder 9)
    - Gay News (Box 185, Folder 10)
    - The New York Review, 12 May 1994 (Box 185, Folder 11)
    - The London Review of Books, August 1980 (Box 185, Folder 12)
    - "My Brilliant Career" -- lecture poster, 1990 (Box 185, Folder 13)
    - The London Review of Books -- excerpt, July/August 1983 (Box 185, Folder 14)
    - Gazette, 3 items. (Box 185, Folder 15)
    - The Times Literary Supplement, 10 October 1980 (Box 186, Folder 2)
    - The London Review of Books, June 1980 (Box 186, Folder 3)
    - The Times Literary Supplement, 25 November 1965 (Box 186, Folder 4)
    - The Art Book: International Publishing Review Ltd, undated (Box 186, Folder 5)
    - The Times Literary Supplement (Box 186, Folder 6)
    - The London Review of Books, April 1981 (Box 186, Folder 7)
    - The London Review of Books, October 1985 (Box 186, Folder 8)
    - The Times Literary Supplement, 23 April 1964 (Box 186, Folder 9)
    - The London Review of Books, March 1990 (Box 186, Folder 10)
    - The London Review of Books (Box 186, Folder 11)
    - The London Review of Books, May 1983 (Box 186, Folder 12)
    - The Times Literary Supplement, 26 July 1963 (Box 186, Folder 13)
    - The London Review of Books, 24 July 1980 (Box 186, Folder 14)
    - The Times: Art Review, 7 February 2004 (Box 186, Folder 15)
    - Calendars (Box 187, Folder 6)
    - Arnolfini Review, September - October 1979 (Box 187, Folder 17)
    - Contrariwise by Peter Blake, 1978 (Box 187, Folder 18)
    - The London Review of Books, 25 October 1979 (Box 187, Folder 19)
    - Article on Akademie der Bildenden Künste Wien, undated (Box 188, Folder 4)
    - Publicity (Box 188, Folder 5)
    - Publicity, 1975 - 1979 (Box 188, Folder 6)
    - Publicity, 1975 - 1979 (Box 188, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous, 1986 - 2006 (Box 216, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous, 1990 - 1996 (Box 216, Folder 2)
    - School of London (Box 216, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous, 1966 - 1985 (Box 216, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous, 1990 - 1993 (Box 216, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous, 1995 (Box 216, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous, 1990 - 1997 (Box 216, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 217, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous, 1994 (Box 217, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous, 1963 - 1990 (Box 217, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous, 1984 - 2008 (Box 217, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous, 2001 (Box 217, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 217, Folder 6)
    - Publicity, 1970 (Box 224, Folder 8)
    - Publicity, 1974 - 1975 (Box 224, Folder 9)
    - Publicity, 1967 (Box 224, Folder 10)
    - Publicity, 1969 (Box 224, Folder 11)
    - Publicity (Box 226, Folder 3)
    - Publicity, 1963 (Box 226, Folder 5)
    - Publicity, 1963 (Box 226, Folder 9)
    - "To hell with the lot of them" by Lucinda Bredin, 25 May 1997; 1 item. (Box 226, Folder 18)
    - The New York Times, 29 September 1997 (Box 227, Folder 1)
    - The New York Times: The Living Arts, 21 September 1998 (Box 227, Folder 2)
    - Forward: Arts & Letters, 21 November 1997 (Box 227, Folder 3)
    - Forward: Arts & Letters, 24 June 1994 (Box 227, Folder 4)
    - The Times: Arts, 21 June 1994 (Box 227, Folder 5)
    - The New York Times: Arts and Leisure, 16 March 1986 (Box 227, Folder 6)
    - The Daily Telegraph: Arts and Books (Box 227, Folder 7)
    - The New York Times: The Living Arts, 24 October 1994 (Box 227, Folder 8)
    - The Daily Telegraph: Arts and Books, 29 May 1998 (Box 227, Folder 9)
    - The New York Times, 19 March 1998; 2 items. (Box 227, Folder 10)
    - The Times: Profile, 23 May 1983 (Box 227, Folder 11)
    - The Sunday Times, 10 February 1963 (Box 227, Folder 12)
    - The Independent, 28 December 2000 (Box 227, Folder 13)
    - Early publicity -- newspapers, 1963 - 1964 (Box 228, Folder 1)
    - Early publicity -- newspapers, 1963 - 1964 (Box 228, Folder 2)
    - Early publicity -- newspapers, 1975 - 1977 (Box 228, Folder 3)
    - Early publicity -- newspapers (Box 228, Folder 4)
    - Early publicity -- newspapers, 1970 - 1978 (Box 228, Folder 5)
    - Early publicity -- newspapers, 1965 (Box 228, Folder 6)
    - Early publicity -- newspapers, 1976 (Box 228, Folder 7)
    - Early publicity -- newspapers, 1978 - 1979 (Box 228, Folder 8)
    - Early publicity -- newspapers (Box 228, Folder 9)
    - Early publicity -- newspapers, 1965 - 1979 (Box 228, Folder 10)
    - Early publicity -- newspapers, 1978 - 1979 (Box 228, Folder 11)
    - Early publicity -- newspapers, 1977 (Box 228, Folder 12)
    - Early publicity -- newspapers, 1975 (Box 228, Folder 13)
    - Publicity -- newspapers (Box 228, Folder 14)
  - Art Works
    - London Review of Books, 17 October 1985; 1 item. (Box 165, Folder 6)
  - Awards
    - University of Durham honorary graduate video (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Chevalier des Arts et Lettres -- photographs and clippings, 1996 (Box 139, Folder 21)
    - Society of Illustrators: Certificate of Merit, undated (Box 153, Folder 28)
  - Exhibits
    - Kitaj in the Aura of Cezanne and other Masters-- gallery proof, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Kitaj in the Aura of Cezanne and other Masters-- images from publication, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Museo de Bellas Artes de Bilbao British Pop publicity dossier, 2005 - 2006 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - International Art Fair 27 catalogue, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Hayward Gallery exhibition catalog (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Art and Technology -- articles, 1969 (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - Art and Technology -- instructions for installation, undated (Box 119, Folder 20)
    - Kitaj: Spain on My Mind -- essay, 2004 (Box 119, Folder 23)
    - Kitaj: Portrait of a Hispanist -- bibliography (Box 119, Folder 24)
    - R.B. Kitaj: Spain in Me -- Memoria, 2004 (Box 124, Folder 5)
    - Kitaj: Retrato de un hispanista -- Dossier de Prensa [press materials], 2004 (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - R.B. Kitaj: A Retrospective -- photographs, 22 items. (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - R.B. Kitaj: A Retrospective -- color slides, 1994; 20 items. (Box 128, Folder 2)
    - R.B. Kitaj: A Retrospective -- press clippings, 1994 (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - R.B. Kitaj: A Retrospective -- correspondence and clippings (1 of 2), 1992 - 1993 (Box 128, Folder 4)
    - R.B. Kitaj: A Retrospective -- correspondence and clippings (2 of 2), 1992 - 1993 (Box 128, Folder 5)
    - R.B. Kitaj: A Retrospective -- correspondence (Box 128, Folder 6)
    - R.B. Kitaj: A Retrospective -- correspondence and publicity (1 of 2), 1994 - 1995 (Box 128, Folder 7)
    - R.B. Kitaj: A Retrospective -- correspondence and publicity (2 of 2), 1994 - 1995 (Box 128, Folder 8)
    - R.B. Kitaj Retrospective -- publicity and reviews (Box 128, Folder 9)
    - R.B. Kitaj Retrospective -- postcards, 1994; 14 items. (Box 128, Folder 10)
    - R.B. Kitaj Retrospective -- correspondence, 1995 - 1998 (Box 128, Folder 11)
    - How to Reach 67 in Jewish Art: 100 Pictures -- reviews and listings, 2000 (Box 128, Folder 12)
    - How to Reach 67 in Jewish Art: 100 Pictures -- color photographs and slides, 2000; 16 items. (Box 128, Folder 13)
    - How to Reach 71 in Jewish Art by R.B. Kitaj -- booklet, 2004 (Box 128, Folder 14)
    - How to Reach 71 in Jewish Art by R.B. Kitaj, 2007 (Box 128, Folder 15)
    - R.B. Kitaj: How to Reach 72 in a Jewish Art, 2005 (Box 128, Folder 16)
    - R.B. Kitaj: How to Reach 72 in a Jewish Art -- press and memorablia, 2005 (Box 128, Folder 17)
    - R.B. Kitaj: Little Pictures -- publicity, 2008 (Box 128, Folder 18)
    - R.B. Kitaj: Little Pictures -- proofs (1 of 2), 2007 (Box 128, Folder 19)
    - R.B. Kitaj: Little Pictures -- proofs (2 of 2), 2007 (Box 128, Folder 20)
    - R.B. Kitaj: Little Pictures -- proof, 2007 (Box 128, Folder 21)
    - Kitaj: In the Aura of Cezanne and Other Masters -- photographs, 2001 - 2002; 21 items. (Box 129, Folder 1)
    - Kitaj: In the Aura of Cezanne and Other Masters -- facsimile of catalog, undated (Box 129, Folder 2)
    - The Artist's Eye -- exhibition materials, 1980 (Box 129, Folder 3)
    - The Artist's Eye -- publicity materials, 1980 (Box 129, Folder 4)
    - The Artist's Eye -- gallery blueprints, 1980 (Box 129, Folder 5)
    - The Artist's Eye -- floor plan, 1980 (Box 129, Folder 6)
    - R. B. Kitaj: Los Angeles Pictures -- L.A. Louver (1 of 3), 2003 (Box 129, Folder 7)
    - R. B. Kitaj: Los Angeles Pictures -- L.A. Louver (2 of 3), 2003 (Box 129, Folder 8)
    - R. B. Kitaj: Los Angeles Pictures -- L.A. Louver (3 of 3), 2003 (Box 129, Folder 9)
    - R. B. Kitaj: Los Angeles Pictures -- catalog preparation, 2003 (Box 129, Folder 10)
    - R.B. Kitaj: Ein Amerikaner in Europe [An American in Europe], 1998 (Box 129, Folder 13)
    - Encounters: New Art From Old, 2000 (Box 129, Folder 14)
    - Chagall to Kitaj: Jewish Experience in 20th Century Art (1 of 2), 1990 - 1991 (Box 129, Folder 15)
    - High and Low: Modern Art and Popular Culture, 1990 (Box 129, Folder 16)
    - Die Spur des Anderen/Traces of Another Self -- Introductory text, 1988 (Box 129, Folder 17)
    - The British Art Show: Old Allegiances and New Directions, 1979 - 1984 (Box 129, Folder 18)
    - Dine, Kitaj -- exhibition materials (1 of 2), 1973 (Box 129, Folder 19)
    - Dine, Kitaj -- exhibition materials (2 of 2), 1973 (Box 129, Folder 20)
    - R.B. Kitaj: Pictures -- proof, 1974 (Box 130, Folder 7)
    - 20th Century British Life Drawing -- catalogue, 1981 (Box 130, Folder 8)
    - Landscape / Cityscape, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 11)
    - Marlborough press release (Box 130, Folder 12)
    - From London -- reviews, 1995 - 1996 (Box 130, Folder 13)
    - Exhibition photographs, undated; 6 items. (Box 130, Folder 14)
    - Exhibition photograph, undated; 1 item. (Box 130, Folder 15)
    - Exhibition photographs, undated; 8 items. (Box 130, Folder 16)
    - Exhibition photographs, undated; 6 items. (Box 130, Folder 17)
    - Photographs of unidentified paintings, undated; 3 items. (Box 130, Folder 18)
    - Kronika/Crónica 2004, Undated. (Box 130, Folder 19)
    - Works on Paper, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 20)
    - Artists Against Racialism Exhibition (World Campaign for the Release of South African Political Prisoners), 1965 (Box 130, Folder 21)
    - Pop Art Graphics, 1969 (Box 130, Folder 22)
    - Gli Amici Pittori di Londra -- correspondence and invitation, 2007 (Box 130, Folder 23)
    - Postcards -- National Gallery, undated (Box 130, Folder 24)
    - Postcards -- miscellaneous, undated (Box 130, Folder 25)
    - Pictures with Commentary / Pictures without Commentary, 1963 (Box 132, Folder 19)
    - Drawn to Cleveland, 2005 (Box 132, Folder 20)
    - R.B. Kitaj -- catalogue, 1989 (Box 132, Folder 34)
    - In Our Time, 1981 (Box 132, Folder 37)
    - R.B. Kitaj: Art and Literature, 1986 (Box 132, Folder 38)
    - Sandra / Two, 1996 (Box 132, Folder 42)
    - Publicity -- 1996 -1997 (1 of 2), Undated. (Box 134)
    - Publicity -- 1990 -1993 (2 of 2), Undated. (Box 134)
    - Publicity -- 1976 - 1988, Undated. (Box 134)
    - Publicity -- 1994 -1996 (2 of 2), Undated. (Box 134)
    - Publicity -- 1996 -1997 (2 of 2), Undated. (Box 134)
    - Publicity -- 1994 -1996 (1 of 2), Undated. (Box 134)
    - Publicity -- 1988 - 1991, Undated. (Box 134)
    - Publicity -- 1990 -1993 (1 of 2), Undated. (Box 134)
    - Publicity -- 1984 - 1989, Undated. (Box 134)
    - Publicity -- 1984 -1986 (2 of 2), Undated. (Box 134)
    - Publicity -- 1990 - 2006 (1 of 2), Undated. (Box 134)
    - Publicity -- 1984 -1986 (1 of 2), Undated. (Box 134)
    - Publicity -- 1990 - 2006 (2 of 2) (Box 134)
    - After Auschwitz: Response to the Holocaust in Contemporary Art, 1995 - 1996 (Box 135, Folder 9)
    - Young Contemporaries -- photocopy of catalog, 1958 (Box 135, Folder 11)
    - A Survey of his Printmaking, 1964-2001, 2002 (Box 135, Folder 21)
    - R.B. Kitaj -- Cleveland retrospective, 1981 - 1982 (Box 135, Folder 28)
    - Frontispiece: Americans Abroad (Box 135, Folder 30)
    - R.B. Kitaj: Paintings and Prints -- catalogue introduction, 1965 (Box 136, Folder 30)
    - Artists Against Racialism Exhibition (World Campaign for the Release of South African Political Prisoners), 1965 (Box 138, Folder 7)
    - School of London -- Private view invitation (Box 138, Folder 20)
    - "Hard-Won" (1 of 2), 1984 (Box 146, Folder 4)
    - R.B. Kitaj: Pastels and Drawings -- catalogue proof (1 of 3), 1980 (Box 149, Folder 11)
    - R.B. Kitaj: Pastels and Drawings -- catalogue proof (2 of 3), 1980 (Box 149, Folder 12)
    - R.B. Kitaj: Pastels and Drawings -- catalogue proof (3 of 3), 1980 (Box 149, Folder 13)
    - R.B. Kitaj: Fifty Drawings and Pastels -- proof (Box 149, Folder 25)
    - Narrative Paintings: Figurative Art of two generations selected by Timothy Hyman, 1979 (Box 149, Folder 29)
    - International Drawing Biennale -- controversy, 1979 (Box 149, Folder 30)
    - The Human Clay: Review by Suzi Gablik, undated (Box 150, Folder 2)
    - Portrait of the Artist as a Mad Scientist by Robert Buhrman, 1969 (Box 150, Folder 3)
    - Exhibition photographs, 4 items. (Box 150, Folder 4)
    - R.B. Kitaj: A Retrospective -- LACMA (1 of 2), 1994 - 1995 (Box 150, Folder 10)
    - R.B. Kitaj: A Retrospective -- Metropolitan Museum (1 of 2), 1995 (Box 150, Folder 11)
    - Joe Tilson & R.B. Kitaj: A Change of He(art) -- exhibit photographs, 1987; 2 items. (Box 150, Folder 12)
    - Unidentified exhibition photographs, undated; 6 items. (Box 150, Folder 13)
    - Notes to the Artist -- Marlborough Gallery, New York, 1995 (Box 150, Folder 14)
    - LACMA -- guest book (1 of 4), 1994 (Box 150, Folder 15)
    - LACMA -- guest book (2 of 4), 1994 (Box 150, Folder 16)
    - LACMA -- guest book (3 of 4), 1994 (Box 150, Folder 17)
    - LACMA -- guest book (4 of 4), 1994 (Box 150, Folder 18)
    - The Artist's Eye -- catalogue proof, 1980 (Box 150, Folder 20)
    - R.B. Kitaj -- catalogue, 1967 (Box 150, Folder 21)
    - R.B. Kitaj: A Print Retrospective -- brochure (Box 150, Folder 22)
    - Announcements and invitations, 1967 - 1979 (Box 150, Folder 23)
    - Announcements and invitations, 1980 - 1989 (Box 150, Folder 24)
    - Announcements and invitations, 1990 - 1999 (Box 150, Folder 25)
    - Announcements and invitations, 1990 - 1999 (Box 150, Folder 26)
    - Announcements and invitations (Box 150, Folder 27)
    - Announcements and invitations, 2000 - 2004 (Box 150, Folder 28)
    - Announcements and invitations, 2004 - 2008 (Box 150, Folder 29)
    - R.B. Kitaj -- Essay draft, 1980 (Box 151, Folder 24)
    - R.B. Kitaj: How to Reach 72 In A Jewish Art -- proof, 2005 (Box 153, Folder 1)
    - R.B. Kitaj: Pictures -- proof (Box 153, Folder 12)
    - R.B. Kitaj: Recent Pictures -- proof, undated (Box 153, Folder 13)
    - Unidentified proofs, undated (Box 153, Folder 14)
    - R.B. Kitaj: Pictures From an Exhibition -- catalogue proof (1 of 4), April - May 1970 (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - R.B. Kitaj: Pictures From an Exhibition -- catalogue proof (2 of 4), April - May 1970 (Box 157, Folder 2)
    - R.B. Kitaj: Pictures From an Exhibition -- catalogue proof (3 of 4), April - May 1970 (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - R.B. Kitaj: Pictures From an Exhibition -- catalogue proof (4 of 4), April - May 1970 (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - Control strips for unidentified catalogue, undated (Box 157, Folder 5)
    - R.B. Kitaj: Recent Pictures -- Color proofs (1 of 5), 1994 (Box 157, Folder 7)
    - R.B. Kitaj: Recent Pictures -- Color proofs (2 of 5), 1994 (Box 157, Folder 8)
    - R.B. Kitaj: Recent Pictures -- Color proofs (3 of 5) (Box 157, Folder 9)
    - R.B. Kitaj: Recent Pictures -- Color proofs (4 of 5), 1994 (Box 157, Folder 10)
    - R.B. Kitaj: Recent Pictures -- Color proofs (5 of 5), 1994 (Box 157, Folder 11)
    - R.B. Kitaj: Art and Literature, 1986; 1 item. (Box 159, Folder 10)
    - Encounters: New Art from Old -- reviews, 2000 (Box 161, Folder 6)
    - R.B. Kitaj: A Retrospective -- proofs (1 of 9), 1994 (Box 162, Folder 1)
    - R.B. Kitaj: A Retrospective -- proofs (2 of 9), 1994 (Box 162, Folder 2)
    - R.B. Kitaj: A Retrospective -- proofs (3 of 9), 1994 (Box 162, Folder 3)
    - R.B. Kitaj: A Retrospective -- proofs (4 of 9), 1994 (Box 162, Folder 4)
    - R.B. Kitaj: A Retrospective -- proofs (5 of 9), 1994 (Box 162, Folder 5)
    - R.B. Kitaj: A Retrospective -- proofs (6 of 9) (Box 162, Folder 6)
    - R.B. Kitaj: A Retrospective -- proofs (7 of 9), 1994 (Box 162, Folder 7)
    - R.B. Kitaj: A Retrospective -- proofs (8 of 9), 1994 (Box 162, Folder 8)
    - R.B. Kitaj: A Retrospective -- proofs (9 of 9), 1994 (Box 162, Folder 9)
    - R.B. Kitaj: A Retrospective -- publicity, 1994 (Box 162, Folder 10)
    - R.B. Kitaj: A Retrospective -- catalogue proofs (Box 163, Folder 1)
    - R.B. Kitaj: A Retrospective -- New York guest book, undated (Box 163, Folder 2)
    - Chagall to Kitaj: Jewish Experience in 20th Century Art (2 of 2), 1990 (Box 165, Folder 1)
    - From London (Box 165, Folder 2)
    - From London, 1995 (Box 165, Folder 3)
    - Què és l'art jueu: De Chagall a Kitaj by Carles Guerra, 1991 (Box 165, Folder 10)
    - 1 Print 1 Painting, undated (Box 166, Folder 1)
    - Flash Art, undated (Box 166, Folder 2)
    - R.B. Kitaj Los Angeles Pictures -- catalogue proofs, 2003 (Box 184, Folder 7)
    - Graphics in the Sixties -- Exhibition poster, 1965 (Box 187, Folder 2)
    - Control strips for unidentified catalogue (Box 187, Folder 15)
    - Pop Art in England: ä einer neuen Figuration, 1947 - 1963 -- Exhibit poster, 1976 (Box 187, Folder 16)
    - The Artist's Eye, 1980 (Box 221, Folder 5)
    - "Hard-Won" (2 of 2), 1984 (Box 224, Folder 1)
    - The State of the Artist by John Russell Taylor, 23 May 1983 (Box 224, Folder 6)
    - Art and Technology -- publicity (Box 224, Folder 7)
    - Prints from London -- poster, 1969 (Box 224, Folder 12)
    - R.B. Kitaj: Complete Graphics, 1963-1969 (Box 224, Folder 15)
    - R.B. Kitaj: An American in Europe -- poster, 1998 (Box 226, Folder 12)
    - Prints: To Benefit the Foundation for Contemporary Performance Arts -- poster, 1995 (Box 226, Folder 16)
    - R.B. Kitaj: A Retrospective -- LACMA (2 of 2), 1994 (Box 238, Folder 4)
    - R.B. Kitaj: A Retrospective -- Metropolitan Museum (2 of 2), 1995 (Box 238, Folder 5)
  - Interviews
    - Artscribe, February 1977 (Box 186, Folder 1)